Luis Gustavo Cruz

Full Stack Developer

\$\ +52-221-417-2669

@ luis.gustavo.contact@gmail.com

∂ https://www.linkedin.com/in/luis-gustavo-cruz-rosales-1383351a1/
∂ https://luisg28.github.io/portfolio-v1/

México ☆ https://github.com/LuisG28

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am Luis Gustavo Cruz Rosales, a web and mobile developer with 3 years of experience in creating efficient and scalable technological solutions. I specialize in the design and development of intuitive and functional applications for both web and mobile platforms. With a strong knowledge of modern technologies and a constant commitment to continuous improvement, I strive to adapt to new challenges and contribute effectively to a wide range of projects.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

TRIPLEI

苗 10/2022 - Present

Mexico city.

Web application development

- Creation and optimization of projects based on requirements.
- Some of these projects were Recruitment, Suite, and Notifications.
- The tools I use are React, JavaScript, and other add-ons for creating
- Development of new features, bug fixing, and report creation.

Web Developer

Hybrido Studio

Development of web and mobile applications

- · I worked on multiple projects using different technologies such as React, React Native, Feathers JS, Postgres SQL, among others.
- Some of these projects were Winko Admin, Winko Front, and Edufarm
- Development of new features, bug fixing, and report generation.

Web Developer

SWPlus

= 05/2019 - 02/2020

Mexico city

Web application development

- Developing projects with JavaScript, .NET, and SQL Server.
- Some of these projects were Recursos Humanos and Tomás Moro eSchool.

EDUCATION

Engineering in Information and Communication Technologies

Technological University of Xicotepec de Juárez.

= 01/2019 - 10/2021

Associate Degree in Information and Communication Technologies, Computer Systems Area.

Technological University of Xicotepec de Juárez.

= 01/2017 - 10/2019

SKILLS

React	Javaso	avascript			Tailwind	
CSS	Typescr	escript		er	Git	
MongoDB React N		ative	Swift			
HTML	NestJs	6				

MY PERSONAL PROJECTS

PORTFOLIO

https://luisg28.github.io/portfolio-v1/en/

Project created to showcase my experience in the development field using different technologies to build web and mobile applications."